Benjamin H. Wolf Papers 5305
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- City of new York vs. Local 1180, CWA, #71-666 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  31B Hearing Transcripts (See Box 31-8 for complete case)
- International Smelting and Refining Co. vs. Local 4985, USA, 4/18/72. #71-647, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  31A Issue, Arbitrator's Notes, Hearing Transcripts, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Work Stoppage
- City Urban Renewal Management Corp. vs. Local 32B SEIU, 5/25/71. #71-668, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  31B Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Negotiation
- Rexon Chemical Corp. vs. Local 447, PSPP, 6/7/71. #71-660, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  Decision, Arbitrator's notes, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Severance Pay
- Gimbel Brothers, Inc. vs. Local 804, IBT, 4/19/71. #71-661 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Transfers, Schedule Change, Insubordination
- Van Blaricom & Co. vs. Local 149, ILGWU, 3/8/71. #71-662, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Submission, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Leaves of Absence, Quits, Probationary Employees
- Shuron Continental vs. Local 330, IUE, 4/71. #71-663, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Submission, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Insubordination, Improper Personal Conduct
- Purolator, Inc. vs. Employees' Union of Purolator 4/71. #71-664, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Settled by Parties at Arbitration hearings
- Case Paper Co., Inc. vs. Local 447, PSPPU, 5/5/71. #71-665, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibit, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Fights & Altercations
- The City of New York vs. Local 1180, CWA, 7/1/71. #71-666, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  Findings of Fact & Recommendations, Fact-Finders Notes, Hearing Transcripts, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Negotiations (See Box 31-B for Hearing Transcripts)
- City of New York (Civil Service Commissions) vs. Local 555, 3/71. #71-667., 1971 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  Arbitrator's Notes, Correspondence - Test Validation
- Simmonds Precision Products vs. Local 452, IUE, 8/71. #71-669, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties During Hearing
- Womeldorf, Inc. vs. Local 707, IBT, 4/71. #71-670, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  Arbitrator's Notes, Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties During Hearing
- Womeldorf, Inc. vs. Local 707, IBT, 5/71. #71-671, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  Decision, Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties During Hearing
- John Stuart, Inc. vs. Local 3, United Storeworkers, RWDSU, #71-672 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Kraft Foods (Parkay Dept.) vs. Local 56, AFAW, 6/71. #71-673, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibit, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Timeliness, Assembly Line Speed
- Reis Manufacturing Co. vs. Local 285, ILGWU, 3/71. #71-674, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- National Realty maintenance Corp. vs. Local 94-94A, IUOE, 5/11/71. #71-675, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Layoffs
- Consumer Farmer Milk Corp. vs. Local 584, IBT. #71-676 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Mamaroneck Board of Education vs. Mamaroneck Teachers Assn., 5/71. #71-677, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  Mediator's Notes, Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Negotiation
- New York State vs. CSEA (State Police Unit) #71-678 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  Correspondence - Contract Negotiations
- The City of Hoboken vs. Local 1078 International Association of Firefighters, 5/10/71. #71-679, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  Report of Recommendations and Fact, Fact Finder's Notes, Employer Exhibit, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Negotiations
- Federal Paper Board Co., Inc. vs. Local 469, PSPPU, 9/20/71. #71-680, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  Arbitrator's Notes, Hearing Transcript, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties
- First National Stores vs. Local 660, IBT. #71-681 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Amperex Electronic Corp. vs. Local 463, IUE, 8/3/71. #71-682, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Seniority, Layoffs, Demotions, Overtime
- Board of Education of the City of new York vs. UFT. #71-683 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Hearing Transcript, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Arbitrability, Bargaining Unit
- Sinclair & Carroll Co., Inc. vs. Local 447, PSPPU, 8/71. #71-684, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Travel Expenses
- Bond Stores Inc. vs. Local 195, ACWA, 8/3/71. #71-685, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Association for Homemakers Service, Inc. vs. Local 1707, CSAEU, 8/27/71. #71-686, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Handicapped Employees
- City of new York vs. Sanitation Department, 3/71. #71-687, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  Notes, Correspondence (re: member of the test validation for promotion to foreman) - Test Validation
- Dobbs Ferry Board of Education vs. Dobbs Ferry Teacher's Association, 5/71. #71-688, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  Mediator's Notes, Correspondence - Contract Negotiation
- Suffolk County vs. Suffolk County Chapter CSEA, 6/3/71. #71-689, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  Decision, Arbitrator's notes, Employee Exhibit, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Red Circle Rates
- Worthington Turbine International vs. Local 1580, IAM, 7/12/71. #71-690, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- National Lead Co. vs. Local 8-3660, OCAW, 8/71. #71-691, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Pelham Central School Dist. Vs. Pelham Teacher's Association, 6/14/71. #71-692, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Leaves of Absences
- Lew Ron Television, Inc. vs. Local 1212, IBEW, 6/15/71. #71-693, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Hiring Hall
- Shop-Rite Supermarkets vs. Local Amalgamated Butchers. #71-694 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Irvington Board of Education vs. Irvington Faculty Association, #71-695 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Time-DC vs. Local 641, IBT, 6/23/71. #71-696, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes Employer Exhibits, Correspondence - Credibility, Discharge, Improper Personal Conduct
- Philip Carey Manufacturing Co. vs. Local 451, UPP, 6/8/71. #71-697, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Schuster's Express, Inc. vs. Local 641, IBT, 7/1/71. #71-697, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Schuster's Express, Inc. vs. Local 641, IBT, 7/1/71. #71-699, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  Correspondence - Alcohol (See Case 71-698)
- Mobil Oil Corp. vs. Independent Oil Workers Union, OCAW, 9/24/71. #71-700, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Sick Leave, Vacations
- Morse Chain Co. vs. Cayuga Lodge 1607, IAM, 6/71. #71-701, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- David Lewis, Inc. vs. ACWA, 7/27/71. #71-702, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Vacation Pay
- Westinghouse Electric Corp. vs. Local 1581, IUE, 11/26/71. #71-703, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Hearing Transcript, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Past Arbitration Award, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibit, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Falsification, Workmen's Compensation
- Port Chester Board of Education, UFSD #4 vs. CSEA, 1/20/72. #71-704, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  Report of Fact & Recommendations, Fact Finder's Notes, Employee Brief, Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Negotiations
- Port Chester Board of Education vs. Post Chester Teachers Association, 7/71. #71-705, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  Mediator's Notes, Correspondence - Contract Negotiation - Mediator Recommends Fact-Finding
- Pepsi-Cola Metropolitan Bottling Co. vs. Local 812, IBT, 8/24/71. #71-706., 1971 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibit, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Leaving Work Area Without Permission, Improper Job Attitude
- Board of Education of North Merrick vs. North Merrick Faculty Association, 8/3/71. #71-701, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  Decision, Arbitrator's notes, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Leaves of Absence
- Standard Steel Sections, Inc. vs. Local 455, IABSOIW, 8/16/71. #71-708, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- DeLaval Turbine, Inc. vs. Local 3355, USA, 2/9/72. #71-709, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Ferndale Farms, Inc. vs. Local 584, IBT, #71-710, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- International Engraving Corporation vs. IUDCCMEH, 9/8/71. #71-711, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Submission, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibit, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Leaves of Absence, Credibility, Quits
- Bayview Nursing Center vs. Local 1115, Jt. Board of Nursing Home & Hospital Division. #71-712. (Box 34, Folder 9)
  Correspondence - Hearings Cancelled
- Concrete Plank, Inc. vs. Local 16, USTCRDWPW, 9/21/71. #71-713, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Wages, Vacation Pay
- City of New York, Office of Labor Relations vs. District Council 37, AFSCME, 11/71. #71-714., 1971 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Assignment to Work Outside Classification
- Rye School Board vs. Rye Teacher's Association, 8/71. #71-715, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  Mediator's Notes, Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Negotiation - Mediator Recommends Holding Off Until Nixon Freeze Lifted - Parties Want Fact-Finding
- Village of Scarsdale vs. Local 540, AFSCME, 9/17/71. #71-716, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Vacancies, Posting, Seniority, Bidding
- Barr Llewellyn Buick Co. vs. Local 316, IBT, 11/3/71. #71-717, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  Decision, Arbitrator's notes, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Quits, Insubordination
- A.S. Beck Shoe Corp vs. Local 108, RWDSU, 8/18/71. #71-718, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Auerbach Bathrobe Co. vs. Local 177, ACWA. #71-719, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Correspondence - Transfer of Business from One Company to Another
- Board of Education of the City of New York vs. UFT, 7/28/72. #71-720, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  Decision, Arbitrator's notes, Hearing Transcript, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Seniority (See Box 35A for Transcripts)
- City of New York vs. Local 1549, District Council #37, AFSCME, 12/14/71. #71-721, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Working Conditions
- Brentwood Board of Education vs. Brentwood Teachers Association, 9/17/71. #71-722, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, memoranda, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Leaves of Absence (Sabbatical)
- Port Chester Union Free Sch. Dist. #4, vs. Port Chester Teachers Association, 11/30/71. #71-723, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  Report of Fact & Recommendations, Fact-Finders Notes, Employee Contract Proposals, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract negotiations
- McCarville Ford, Inc. vs. Local 259, UAW, 9/8/71. #71-724, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Court Case, Correspondence - Vacation, Seniority, Past Practice
- Allied new York Maintenance Corp. vs. Local 553, IBT, 9/71. #71-725., 1971 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Dresser Industries, Inc. vs. Lodge 1644, IAM, #71-726 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  Correspondence - Hearing Temporarily Postponed
- Eazor Express vs. Local 560, IBT, 11/4/71. #71-727, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Hearing Transcript, Employer Brief, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Carelessness (See Box 35A for Transcript)
- The City of new York vs. Local 1199, RWDSU, 12/71. #71-728, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  Report of Recommendations of Impasse Panel, Chairman of Panel's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Hearing Transcript, Correspondence - Contract Negotiations (See Box 35A for Transcripts)
- Norman Oldsmobile, Inc. vs. Local 259, UAW, 10/7/71. #71-729, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Past Arbitration Award, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Suspension, Incompetence
- Port Chester UFSD #4, vs. CSEA, #71-730 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  Fact-Finding (No information available on the case)
- International Paper Co., Tonawanda Mill vs. Local 241, UPP, 9/17/71. #71-731, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibit, Employee Exhibit (Photographs), Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Assault (Fights & Altercations)
- Hooker Chemical Corp. vs. Lodge 2112, IAM, 10/28/71. #71-732, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Post-Hearing Brief, Employee Post-Hearing Brief, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Assignment to Work Outside Classification, Bargaining Unit Work
- Hygrade Iron Works, Inc. vs. Local 455, IAM, 9/2/71. #71-734, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Allied Building Cleaning Corp. & Alexander's Department Store vs. Local 30, IUOE, 10/12/71. #71-735, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employers memos of Law, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Theft
- Northwest Airlines vs. IAM, #71-737 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  Correspondence - Hearing Postponed
- Yorktown Board of Education vs. Yorktown Teachers Association, #71-738 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Midwest Freight vs. Local 560, IBT, 12/23/71. #71-739, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Correspondence - Drinking & Intoxication
- Capital City Container Co. vs. Albany Local 2, 10/71. #71-740, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  Correspondence - Absences
- Standard Brands, Inc. vs. Local 142, OPEIU, 11/71. #71-742, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Vacations
- Western Electric Co., Inc. vs. Local 80, AFTE, 1/7/72. #71-743, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Hearing Transcript, Employer's Post Hearing Brief, Past Arbitration Awards, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Incompetence & Inefficiency
- American Cyanamid Co. vs. Local 111, ICWU, 12/15/71. #71-744, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Intoxication, Employees' Rights
- Direct Mail Contract Association vs. District 65, RWDSU, 1/25/72. #71-745, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties During Hearing
- Children's Village vs. Children's Village Association, 12/71. #71-748, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  Mediator's Notes, Contract, Correspondence - Contract Negotiations (Settled by Parties During Hearing)
- Breyers Ice Cream vs. Local 757, IBT, 3/72. #71-749, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Jurisdiction
- Associated Coca-Cola Bottling Co. vs. Local 65, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  CTWH, 12/28/71. #71-750 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibits,Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Management Rights
- City of Rochelle vs. New Rochelle Police Benefit Association, 12/30/71, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  (Part of Box titled 36A Folder 1(A-E))#71-746 Report of Fact & Recommendations, Fact-Finders Notes, Employer Brief, Miscellaneous Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Management Rights
- City of New Rochelle vs. Uniformed Fire Fighters Association, 12/27/71., 1971 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  [Part of Box entitled "36A" folder 2(A-E)] Report of fact & Recommendations, Fact Finders Notes, Employer Brief, Employer Opening Statement, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Miscellaneous Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Negotiation
- City of New Rochelle vs. Local 663, AFSCME, 1/4/72., 1972 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  [Folder entitled 1(A-B)] #71-751 Report of Fact & Recommendations, Fact Finders Notes, Employer Memorandum, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Negotiation
- City of New Rochelle vs. CSEA (New Rochelle Unit) 1/7/72. #71-752, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  Report of Fact and Recommendation, Fact Finder's Notes, Employer Memorandum, Correspondence - Contract Negotiation
- Eastern Freightways, Inc. vs. Local 560, IBT, 11/71., 1971 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  #71-753 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Correspondence - Negligence and Carelessness
- Getty Oil Co. vs. PTEU, 3/1/72, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  [Folder entitled 4(A-D)] Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Hearing Transcript, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Assault (Fights & Altercations), Burden of Proof
- Strippit Houdaille vs. Local 1691, IAM, 11/1/71., 1971 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  #71-755 Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties
- Shuron Continental vs. Local 330, IUE, 12/71., 1971 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  #71-756 Correspondence
- Highland Telephone Co. vs. Local 503, IBEW, 2/26/72. #71-757, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employer Post-Hearing Brief & Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Bidding, Demotions
- Board of Education of the City of New York vs. UFT, 6/6/72, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  "71-758" Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Hearing Transcripts, Employee Brief, Past Arbitration Award, Employer Exhibits, Correspondence - Arbitrability, Grievance Procedure
- Bedford Board of Education vs Bedford Teacher's Association, 2/23/72, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  [Folder entitled 2(A-D)]#71-759 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Submissions, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Assignment of Jobs, Contract Modification, Vacancies, Bargaining Unit.
- Lehman Optical Co., Inc. vs. Local 408, UOWU, 1/14/72., 1972 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  #71-760 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Submissions, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Vacation, Sick Leave, Severance Pay.
- National Lead Industries vs. Local 343, IUE, 1/27/72., 1972 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  #71-761 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Fights and Altercations (Assault)
- Albert Wepper Corp. vs. Local 365, UAW, 12/13/71., 1971 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  #71-762 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Falsification
- Restaurant Associates Industries, Inc. vs. Local 71, TTICFE. (Box 38, Folder 6)
  #71-763 Correspondence - Hearing Postponed
- Board of Education of the City of New York vs. UFT, 7/13/72, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  [Folder Entitled 7(A-B)] Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Hearing Transcript, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Correspondence - Remedies (Awards), Bargaining Unit
- Universal Atlas Cement Division vs. Local 106-106B IUOE, 2/22/72, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  [Folder entitled 8(A-B)] #71-765 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Grievance Procedure, Shift Scheduling
- Nescoe Steel Barrel Co. vs. Local 641, Merchandise Drivers Union, 1/10/72, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  #71-766 Arbitrator's Notes, Correspondence - Settled at Hearing
- V.P. Sealand Service, Inc. vs. Local 153, OPEIU, 2/22/72, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  [Folder entitled 1(A-B)] Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Timeliness, Absences, Tardiness, Severance Pay
- Aeroflex Laboratories, Inc. vs. Local 5, Plastic Workers, 1/14/72., 1972 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  [Folder entitled 2(A-B)]#71-769 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Correspondence - Absences
- World Plastics Extruders, Inc. vs. Local 5, Plastic Workers, 1/14/72., 1972 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  #71-769 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Correspondence - Absences
- City of New York vs. District Council 37, AFCSME, 12/71., 1971 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  #71-770 Correspondence - Mutually Selected by Parties
- New York University Medical Center vs. Local 810, IBT, 1/72, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  #71-771 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Correspondence - Negligence, Insubordination
- Fedders Corp. vs. Local 483, IUE, 1/28/72., 1972 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  #71-772 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Transfers
- Queens Farm Diary vs. Local 584, IBT, 12/28/71, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  #71-773 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Correspondence - Fighting
- Stauffer Chemical Co. vs. Local 1628, UAW, 2/72, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  #71-774 Correspondence
- Flight Line Inc. vs. Local 365, UAW, 1/11/72., 1972 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  [Folder entitled 9(A-B)] #71-775 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Strike
- Harry M. Stevens, Inc. vs. Local 325, HREBIU, 2/22/72, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  [Folder entitled 10(A-B)] #71-776 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Past Arbitration Award Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Improper Work Practices
- Lakeland Board of Education vs. Lakeland Federation of Teachers, 2/1/72, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  [Folder entitled 11(A-B)] #71-777 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Past Arbitration Award, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Leaves of Absence, Past Practice
- City of New York (Police Administrative Aides) vs. District Council #37, Local 1549, AFSCME, 4/11/72, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  #71-778 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibit, Correspondence - Job Description, Transfers
- Continental Baking Co. vs. Local 194, IBT, 1/26/72, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  [Folder entitled 13(A-B)] #71-779 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Past Arbitration Award, Employee Exhibit, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Schedules of Work, Past Practice
- United States Printing Ink Corp. vs. Local 447, IPPAUNA, 1/31/72, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  #72-1 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibit, Correspondence I Inability to Work, Termination of Employment
- Point Pleasant Beach Board of Education vs. Point Pleasant Beach Teachers Association 3/72, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  #72-2 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Correspondence - Violation of Contract, Timeliness, Grievance Procedure
- St. Regis Paper Co. vs. Local 4867, USA, 3/28/72, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibit, Employee Exhibit, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Promotion, Bargaining Unit, Temporary Assignment
- Knapp Engraving Co., Inc. vs. NYLPEU, 3/15/72, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  #72-4 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibit, Employee Exhibit, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Lay offs, Discrimination
- Directo Sales, Inc. vs. Local 810, IBT, 3/16/72, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  #72-5 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Leaving Plant Without Permission, Improper Personal Conduct
- Beaunit Corp. vs. Local 2207, UTWA, 1971-1972 (Box 40, Folder 6)